<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>Restored Monsters Pack Dev</name>
    <directory>restoredmonsterspack</directory>
    <id>3239551710</id>
    <description>Forgotten enemies have returned to the basement! Restored Monsters Pack is a mod that adds enemies ranging from unused monsters left in Repentance to new enemies based of developer concepts

[img]https://i.imgur.com/t58xA5L.png[/img]

[h2]Features[/h2]
[b]30+ enemies[/b], ranging from unused monsters left in Repentance to new enemies based of developer concepts
A [b]new TNT[/b] variant
[b]Many new rooms[/b], with some from the original Antibirth mod
[b]Reworks and polishing[/b] of some of the enemies from their previous iterations (No more Dumplings camping rocks!)
[b]Compatibility:[/b] This mod has extra compatibility with Last Judgement, Revelations, Fall from Grace, and THE FUTURE. 
You can read more about the enemies added by this mod on our wiki! ( https://moddingofisaac.wiki.gg/wiki/Restored_Mods )

[h2]Caution![/h2]
[b][u][url=https://repentogon.com]REPENTOGON[/url] is required for this mod to function. It will (probably) not work without it![/u][/b]

Don't want to use REPENTOGON+ or Last Judgement? Try [url=]Restored Monsters: Judgement Free[/url]!

[b][u]The following mods are included in some form within Restored Monsters Pack, and should not be used in conjunction with it:[/u][/b]
    
Cut Monsters 
Antibirth Monsters 
Antibirth Minus by [url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198081320400]Sinbiscuit[/url]
Strifers by [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/PixelPlz]PixelPlz[/url]
Corpse Eaters by [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/PixelPlz]PixelPlz[/url]
Dumplings by [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/24chrome]24Chrome[/url], [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/jubbalub]Jubbalub[/url], and [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/We_Strvn]We Strvn[/url]
Ghost Babel by [url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198081320400]Sinbiscuit[/url]


[h2]Contributors[/h2] 
We Strvn, Sillst, Redstinger, Pandora, InfiniteCosmos, Kittenchilly, Mr. R, Kerkel, vor_kakisha, Acexolotl, Goganidze, Michael8587, Watchmeojo, Skelej64, Lesser_Star, ENFOR, PixelPls, Lazarus, Firework, Brakedude, Orange Ice Pop, Reixen, steve2552, Pinchalin, TheReturnofGarnk, and JaRo7126.


[h2]Special thanks to[/h2] 
[code][u]Public Entertainment Networked Interactive Software[/u] - For the original Antibirth mod as well as the content and concepts that this mod builds off of[/code]
 

[h2]Restored Hub Discord Link[h2]
https://discord.gg/BYGmAhgG8k

</description>
    <version>1.13</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Rooms"/>
    <tag id="Floors"/>
    <tag id="Enemies"/>
    <tag id="Hazards"/>
    <tag id="Graphics"/>
</metadata>
